what I want to do is I want to go over
我想做的是我想过去
some of the things you might notice
您可能会注意到的一些事情
straightaway when you first open up the
当您第一次打开
open up the updated IDE there are a few
打开更新的IDE有一些
things that I noticed as a certainly as
我注意到的肯定是
a Java person when I first started using
刚开始使用Java的人
IntelliJ 15 for example and in my driver
例如IntelliJ 15和我的驱动程序
tests in particular it was pretty good
测试特别好
at pointing out to me where I had
向我指出我在哪里
duplicated code which is a little bit
重复的代码有点
alarming but that's the way it goes so
令人震惊，但事实就是如此
here you can see it says found
在这里你可以看到它说找到
duplicated code in this file if I press
如果按此文件中的重复代码
alt enter it will allow me to navigate
alt输入它将允许我导航
to the duplicates now this will show
到重复项现在将显示
duplicate code of over five lines of
超过五行的重复代码
code I can also configure it according
代码我也可以根据它进行配置
to the way you can figure any inspection
以您可以进行任何检查的方式
so I can turn it off or I can tweak the
所以我可以将其关闭或调整
inspection to sort of say well I don't
检查有点说我不
really care about duplicate code in
真的很在乎重复的代码
tests for example or I only care about
例如测试或我只在乎
it in a particular scope or I might want
它在特定范围内或者我可能想要
to set it for morning up to a more
将其设置为早上或更长时间
severe error so like any ins and it can
严重的错误，所以像任何ins，它可以
be completely configured you can get rid
完全配置即可摆脱
of it of course by refactoring out that
当然是通过重构
you can put a coat and this should be
你可以穿一件外套，这应该是
something this should be reasonably
这应该是合理的
familiar to to most people who've been
大多数去过的人都熟悉
using the refactoring tools anyway let's
无论如何，使用重构工具
say we extract this into a method and
说我们将其提取为一种方法，
let's call it check it herbal extracts
我们称它为草药提取物
out into our method this is the only
进入我们的方法，这是唯一的
thing that changes between the code so
在代码之间发生变化的东西
put this into a parameter and as per
将其放入参数并按照
usual IntelliJ IDEA will find the
通常IntelliJ IDEA会找到
duplicate code and offer to replace it
重复代码并提出替换它
for you so now I have two tests which
对你来说，现在我有两个测试
are calling the same method and and so
正在调用相同的方法，依此类推
my duplicate coders has been reduced to
我重复的编码器已减少为
a single method which is called with two
一个被两个调用的方法
different parameters now something you
现在不同的参数你
might have noticed when I'm looking at
当我看着时可能已经注意到
this test is that I've got little run
这个测试是我很少跑
icons in my in the gutter and it shows
槽中我的图标，它显示
me that last time I ran this test
我上次我进行这项测试
everything went green everything's okay
一切都变绿了，一切都还好
let me show you an example of a test
让我给你看一个测试的例子
where I haven't run it yet so let's take
我还没有运行它的地方，让我们来
a look at some arbitrary test
看一些随意的测试
here it shows me where I can that I can
在这里，它告诉我在哪里我可以
run it so I can run it I can debug it I
运行它，以便我可以运行它，我可以调试它，
can run it with coverage if I run it
如果我运行它可以覆盖运行
then in my case because this is a
那么在我的情况下，因为这是一个
greater project like this and adoption
这样更大的项目并获得采用
to run it as a gradual or j unit
以逐步或j单位运行
configuration once I've run it then it
配置一旦运行就可以了
will tell me that that all the tests
会告诉我所有的测试
went green there and then of course I
去那里绿色，然后我当然
can rerun a test from here I can run
可以从这里重新运行测试
individual tests or debug individual
单个测试或调试单个
tests as well or not a bit completely
测试还是完全没有
ignores let's try this one oh I know why
忽略让我们尝试这个哦，我知道为什么
I window that opens all my other monitor
我打开所有其他监视器的窗口
which is not super useful okay so now i
这不是超级有用，所以现在我
have i already had a number of different
我已经有一些不同的
ways i could run tests or configurations
我可以运行测试或配置的方式
but this is just another one and so what
但这只是另一个，所以
I found really useful about this is when
我发现这真的很有用
I'm running my test I can see I can see
我正在运行测试，我可以看到，我可以看到
the status of all my tests the last time
上次我所有测试的状态
they ran or if perhaps I haven't run
他们跑了，或者也许我还没跑
them obviously if one of these tests
他们显然，如果这些测试之一
fails let's turn this to false and then
失败，我们将其设置为false，然后
try running it then
然后尝试运行它
one is going to change to a failure icon
一个将更改为失败图标
while we're on the subject of testing
在我们进行测试的时候
let's have a look at the new you I'd for
让我们来看看我想要的新产品
testing so it's well it's not so much a
测试，所以很好，不是很多
brand new UI it's just an updated
全新的用户界面，它只是一个更新
version of the UI I'm going to run all
UI版本，我将全部运行
the tests too so that we can see the
测试也是如此，以便我们可以看到
results down here like new now
结果在这里像现在一样新
previously you could get the statistics
以前你可以得到统计数据
for a test in a separate panel with a
用于在带有
separate table telling you what time it
单独的表格告诉您几点
took to run individual tests and so
进行个别测试，所以
forth now I get the time taken to run
现在，我有时间去跑步
the tests in line with the actual test
测试与实际测试相符
themselves so I can also do something
自己，所以我也可以做点什么
like I can reorder the tests by time
就像我可以按时间重新排列测试
taken so i can look at the long one and
采取，所以我可以看看长的和
find out finally to do something to make
终于找到要做的事情
that take slightly less time if that
如果花费的时间少一点
sort of thing that's interested in
感兴趣的东西
interesting to me one of the other
对我来说很有趣
things I can do with my update is test
我可以执行的更新测试
panel is I can now place this on the
面板是我现在可以将其放在
left or the right of the UI I don't just
我不只是在界面的左侧还是右侧
always have to have it on the bottom so
总是必须把它放在最下面
if I put it on the only find it now oh
如果我现在把它放到唯一找到的哦
no sorry I'm looking at the wrong place
不好意思我看错地方了
I can move this to the right hand side
我可以将其移到右侧
and it will automate automatically
它会自动自动化
figure out now running on the right the
找出现在在右边运行
best price put the consult is down
最优惠的价格请咨询
underneath the best themselves so I have
在最好的自己之下，所以我有
a bit more versatility around how I
关于我的操作方式更具通用性
display my test results depending on
显示我的测试结果取决于
obviously screen layout and so forth
显然是屏幕布局等等
there are other things I can do with my
我还有其他事情可以做
test results for example I can export
测试结果，例如我可以导出
them I can export them as HTML XML
我可以将它们导出为HTML XML
obviously this is useful for saving test
显然，这对于保存测试很有用
results or for sharing specific results
结果或共享特定结果
with the team so on and so forth and the
与团队等等，等等
other thing i can do is i can look at
我可以做的另一件事是我可以看
all the tests that i've run in the past
我过去进行的所有测试
when i ran them and so i can reopen this
当我运行它们时，我可以重新打开它
and have a look at the test results
看看测试结果
let's pick a different sort of test and
让我们选择另一种测试
so the test results will I won't have to
这样测试结果就不必了
rerun the test in order to look at a
重新运行测试以查看
previous set of test results so I can
先前的测试结果集
see that that test result and when it
看到那个测试结果以及何时
failed
失败了
one of the other major efforts here is
这里的其他主要努力之一是
to try and make this testing this
尝试对此进行测试
testing you I much more consistent
测试你我更加一致
across all the different frameworks and
跨所有不同的框架
libraries that that you're using so for
您正在使用的库
example if you're running a JavaScript
如果您运行的是JavaScript
testing framework you'll find it very
测试框架，您会发现它非常
similar and very familiars it's very
相似且非常熟悉
easy to move from libraries and
易于从图书馆和
languages and you get a similar sort of
语言，您会得到类似的结果
experience inside the IDE and one final
在IDE中的经验和最终体验
thing around running applications or
运行应用程序或
tests let's let me switch to another
测试让我们切换到另一个
another project if i'm running a
如果我正在运行另一个项目
long-running service or long running
长期运行或长期运行
tests let me start this one up then my
测试让我开始这一步，然后我的
run icon changes to a rerun icon so that
运行图标更改为重新运行图标，以便
it's more clear to me that I'm already
对我来说更清楚的是我已经
running this service and if I want to
运行此服务，如果我想
run it again I will shut this service
再次运行它将关闭此服务
down and restart it that's particularly
关闭并重新启动它，特别是
useful for an application like this one
对于这样的应用程序很有用
where I have four or five different
我有四个或五个不同的地方
services and I quite often want to
服务，我经常想
restart individual services I don't
重新启动我不提供的个别服务
necessarily want to start a brand new
一定要开始一个全新的
version and there's one more area I want
版本，还有我想要的一个区域
to cover in this section which is if i
在本节中涵盖
look at finding path then there's now
看着寻找道路，然后有
the ability to preview the search
预览搜索的能力
results so let's say i want to search
结果，假设我要搜索
for all lambdas in my project for some
对于我项目中的所有lambda
reason then in the preview tab I can see
原因，然后在预览选项卡中我可以看到
everywhere where i'm using the little
我在用小东西的任何地方
under Chevron which might not always be
在雪佛龙（Chevron）下
an actual lambda so I can kind of flick
一个实际的lambda，所以我可以轻弹一下
through take a look and see if this is
通过看看，看看这是
this is the thing I want to navigate to
这是我想导航到的东西
or if this is perhaps misleading because
或如果这可能是误导的，因为
in this case it's a regular expression
在这种情况下，这是一个正则表达式
not a lambda and then of course I can
不是lambda，那我当然可以
navigate directly to that
直接导航到
one last thing around UI improvements
关于UI改进的最后一件事
which I particularly liked and is
我特别喜欢的是
particularly since since i'm actually
特别是因为我实际上
colorblind there's a option to change
色盲有改变的选择
the UI to be much more friendly to
用户界面要友好得多
colorblind people like me so i can
像我这样的色盲人，我可以
change it to something where it will be
将其更改为将要存在的内容
less dependent upon reds and greens to
减少对红色和绿色的依赖
show me the differences between
告诉我之间的区别
different things in the UI i've been
我去过的用户界面中的不同事物
playing with us a little bit myself it's
和我自己玩一点
quite interesting as a colorblind person
作为一个色盲人很有趣
to see how many ques you've been missing
看你丢失了多少个问题
because things were shown in red and
因为事物以红色显示，
green and orange and you weren't aware
绿色和橙色，您不知道
of them so if you are colorblind I
如果你是色盲我
highly recommend turning on this setting
强烈建议打开此设置
and if there's anything that you want to
如果有什么想
see then feeding back to to jetbrains
看到然后反馈到水脑
and seeing and how we can improve this
以及如何改善这一点
particular feature I think this is
我认为这是特别的功能
really interesting i'm going to be using
真的很有趣，我将要使用
a lot more from now on so that's kind of
从现在开始还有更多
the brief intro to editor and UI changes
编辑器和UI更改的简短介绍
that should be those they should be
那应该是那些
fairly obvious to you as soon as you
对您而言，对您而言相当明显
start using the UI as always we have a
像往常一样开始使用UI
number of improvements to the debugger
调试器的改进数量
so particularly around lambda
所以特别是在lambda周围
expressions so let's have a quick look
表达式，让我们快速浏览
at what that looks like so here for
在这里看起来像什么
example I have a stream this would be a
例如我有一个流，这将是一个
fairly common use of stream where I have
我有流的相当普遍的用途
a stream and a number of lambda
一条小溪和一些lambda
expressions going into a number of my
表达进入我的许多
stream operations now over here on the
现在在这里进行流操作
gutter on the left hand side I can
我可以在左边装订
actually see a little lambda icon and it
实际看到一个小lambda图标，它
shows me the type of the lambda now I
告诉我现在的lambda类型
find this particularly useful because
觉得这特别有用，因为
now I've started using members in Java 8
现在我开始在Java 8中使用成员
a lot more you find a lot of the types
您会发现很多类型
kind of disappear because compiler can
之所以消失，是因为编译器可以
work them out but as a developer you
解决它们，但作为开发人员
can't always work them out and this is
不能总是解决它们，这是
useful this is telling me that map takes
有用的是，这告诉我地图需要
a function is telling me that filter
一个功能告诉我那个过滤器
types of predicates so I can see that in
predicate的类型，所以我可以看到
the IDE really easily now I might want
我现在可能想要IDE非常容易
to do this lambda so I'm going to look
做这个lambda，所以我要看
specifically at at this particular
特别是在这个特定的
lambda I can either choose to put the
lambda我可以选择放
breakpoint up at the top level so i can
在最高级别上设置断点，这样我就可以
break point when when the stream is
当流是
initiated or just on the individual
发起或仅针对个人
lambda now this is much more useful i
lambda现在这更有用了
mean that's very useful is the when you
就是说，当您
have more than one lambda on the line
在线上有多个lambda
so if I price oppressed place a break
所以如果我压价了就休息一下
point here then I can put a break point
指向这里，然后我可以放置一个断点
on any one of these individual Landers
在这些登陆器中的任何一个上
so let's say I put a break point on this
所以说我在此设置了一个断点
farm now let's navigate to the test and
现在，让我们导航到测试
try and debug this
尝试调试
so now you can see the breakpoint stops
所以现在您可以看到断点停止了
on the map operation was specifically
在地图上的操作是专门
the lambda to turn it into a lowercase
将其变成小写的lambda
letter or locate word and as I step
字母或定位词，然后按我的步骤
through then I see each time that lambda
通过那时，我每次看到那个lambda
is called with a different word one of
用另一个词之一
the other things that we've implemented
我们已经实现的其他事情
is the ability to run to cursor inside a
是在光标内运行光标的能力
lambda so if I put my cursor on a lambda
lambda，所以如果我将光标放在lambda上
in the filter method for example and
例如在过滤方法中
then I run this oops and then I run to
然后我跑这个哎呀，然后我跑到
break point that would be useful it will
有用的断点，它将
break in that lambda where I put my
闯入我放我的那个lambda
cursor so this gives me a lot more
光标，所以这给了我更多
flexibility around debugging lambda
调试lambda的灵活性
expressions particularly in stream
表达特别是流
operations where you have a number of
您有很多操作的地方
different lambda operations and I might
不同的lambda操作，我可能
be wanting to see the inputs of any
想要看到任何输入
particular stage of my of my stream
我流中的特定阶段
pipeline so let's let this finish and
流水线，所以让我们完成
i'll finally they show you the next
我终于会告诉他们下一个
change in the debugger that i want to
更改我想要的调试器
show you so one of the other
告诉你另一个
new features is let's debug this again
新功能让我们再次调试
but this time we'll stop further will
但是这次我们将进一步停止
stop and closer to the beginning of the
停下来，靠近起点
method now what I might want to do
现在我可能想做的方法
especially if i'm debugging are more
特别是如果我正在调试更多
complicated set of method chain of
方法链的复杂集合
method calls what i might want to do is
方法调用我可能想做的是
I might want a particular method to
我可能想要一种特定的方法
finish early and return asset value so
尽早完成并返回资产价值，以便
here I've got a new feature which allows
在这里，我有一个新功能
force return so it won't evaluate any
强制返回，因此不会进行任何评估
more of the rest of this method it will
该方法的其余部分将更多
return at this point manager is going to
此时经理将返回
ask me what value do you want to return
问我你想返回什么价值
because this is supposed to return a
因为这应该返回一个
movie message so let's say I return new
电影讯息，所以说我返回新
moody message oh and then it will also
喜怒无常的消息哦，然后它也会
give me the autocomplete that I expect
给我我期望的自动完成功能
to have now if I put a null in there
现在，如果我在其中放一个null
it'll carry on running but my test will
它会继续运行，但我的测试会
fail because I've got a null pointer so
失败，因为我有一个空指针，所以
this is particularly useful for instead
这对于代替特别有用
of having to tweak variables or values
必须调整变量或值
inside a specific class or method in
在特定的类或方法中
order to force a method to return
为了强制方法返回
something specifically I can do the
我可以专门做的事情
force return and tell it which value to
强制返回并告诉它要使用哪个值
return one final thing which is not
返回最后一件不是
specifically around the debugger but
特别是围绕调试器，但
does kind of help with understanding
对理解有所帮助
what's going on inside the code is the
代码里面发生的是
ability to evaluate the expression types
评估表达类型的能力
inside a lambda so here i can say i'm
在lambda中，所以在这里我可以说我
going to take the s to locate expression
将使用s定位表达式
and it's going to tell me that this is a
会告诉我这是一个
string type and this is available in
字符串类型，这在
scholar before but now it's available
学者以前，但现在可用
for java 8 lambdas and for groovy as
对于Java 8 lambdas和groovy作为
well so again like the other like the
好，再像另一个一样
other tweaks and changes like the
其他调整和更改，例如
ability to debug lambdas like this and
像这样调试lambda的能力
showing you what type the land is I just
告诉你我只是哪种土地
get a lot more feedback from the idea
从这个想法中获得更多反馈
about what's going on inside my java 8
关于我的Java 8内部发生了什么
specific features there's also been a
具体功能也有
number of changes around the version
版本周围的更改数量
control side of things some of them are
某些方面的控制权
just small improvements to help with our
只是小小的改进，以帮助我们
workflow some of them are new features
其中一些是新功能
that we didn't have previously so
我们以前没有的
firstly I'm
首先我是
going to look at rebasing obviously
显然要考虑重新定基
different teams like to work in
不同的团队喜欢一起工作
different ways so not everyone uses
不同的方式，所以不是每个人都使用
rebase not everyone uses much but what
改组不是每个人都使用很多，但是
we've done is we've turned rebase into a
我们已经完成了，我们已经将改组变成了
feature which is at a sort of par with
可以与之媲美的功能
merging so for example I'm on this
合并，例如，我在此
branch branch to rebase now if I click
如果我单击，分支分支现在要重新设置基准
on this branch here my IntelliJ 15
在此分支上，我的IntelliJ 15
branch I can rebase onto this branch the
分支，我可以基于这个分支
same way as I could have merged onto
与我可以合并到的方式相同
previously so if i press this it should
以前所以如果我按这个应该
allow me to rebase straightaway i get
让我立即变基我得到
the same functionality if I want to I
如果我想要相同的功能
can do it from the log as well so for
也可以从日志中完成
example I can do the rebase in the inner
例子我可以在内部做基础
VCS log too so it just basically allows
VCS日志也是如此，因此基本上
you to rebase the same way that you can
您将以相同的方式进行基准调整
merge with the same sort of ease of use
合并具有相同的易用性
this also works if you've got a project
如果您有一个项目，这也可以
with multiple VCS roots then you can
具有多个VCS根，则可以
also rebase across those too so this is
也会在这些基础上重新定位，所以这是
this can be quite powerful feature
这可能是非常强大的功能
particularly for more complex projects
特别是对于更复杂的项目
than this one one of the other new
比另一个新的
features is the ability in the there are
功能是其中的能力
various different diffuse that you have
您拥有的各种不同的扩散
inside IntelliJ IDEA sometimes you're
在IntelliJ IDEA中有时
comparing against an older version of
与旧版本的进行比较
the file sometimes you're doing a diff
该文件有时您正在做比较
on check in and and the we've made those
在检查中，我们已经做了那些
different types of disks and more
不同类型的磁盘等等
consistent so that you can actually edit
一致，以便您实际上可以进行编辑
inside the inside the diff fewer so that
内部差异比较少，这样
you can edit your local file there there
您可以在那里编辑本地文件
in the de fewer so that's one small
在较少的，所以这是一个小
change and another thing is we've added
变化，另一件事是我们添加了
the ability to undo when you're in the
在您处于撤消状态的能力
middle of a merge and then we've added
合并的中间，然后我们添加了
two new features for for other systems
其他系统的两个新功能
so for example you can shelve in
例如，您可以搁置
perforce so when you do shelf you're not
坚持，所以当你做架子时，你不会
necessarily just saving on your local
一定只是节省您的本地
shelf if you've got a perforce force
如果您有强力，则上架
project you can shell in perforce so
您可以在perforce中安装项目
it's much safer much much less likely to
它更安全，几乎不可能
lose those changes and another feature
丢失这些更改和另一个功能
we've added is the ability to manage
我们增加了管理能力
patchy
斑驳的
in mercurial cues as well as always
一如既往地
frameworks aren't standing still while
框架并没有停滞不前
we create the IDE so we've added
我们创建了IDE，所以我们添加了
additional support for updated
对更新的附加支持
frameworks so are so intelligent 8 with
框架是如此智能8
with frameworks as they go so for
随着他们去的框架
example spring 4.2 we've added coding
在示例Spring 4.2中，我们添加了编码
assistance for spring 4.2 features we've
我们已经为Spring 4.2提供了帮助
added code coding assistance for spring
为spring添加了代码编码帮助
boot features we've improved the project
引导功能，我们已经改善了项目
wizard for spring boot as well there
那里的 spring boot 向导
will be a separate webinar later on
稍后将是一个单独的网络研讨会
around the spring specific features so I
围绕春天的特色，所以我
don't want to spend too much time
不想花太多时间
looking at those because they are a big
看着那些，因为它们很大
enough project in their own right to
自己拥有足够的项目权
have their own webinar in terms of
有自己的网络研讨会，
Grails 3 we have support for girls 3 now
Grails 3我们现在支持女孩3
and the Android users will be very happy
Android用户将会非常高兴
to hear that the updates in Android
听到Android中的更新
studio 1.3 or 1.4 have been merged into
Studio 1.3或1.4已合并到
IntelliJ 15 as well but the two features
IntelliJ 15也一样，但有两个功能
I specifically want to look at and
我特别想看看
demonstrate today are around our Killian
今天演示在我们的基利安附近
testing and the docker support so let's
测试和Docker支持，让我们
have a quick look at I'll kill you I
快速浏览一下，我会杀了你
shall switch to one of my projects which
将切换到我的项目之一
has right right setup so here I've
有正确正确的设置，所以我在这里
gotten arquillian tested so you can see
经过Arquillian测试，所以您可以看到
and as with the previous test I have the
和以前的测试一样，
ability to to run these tests with
具有运行这些测试的能力
different configurations so I'm going to
不同的配置，所以我要
run this one unlike the other project
运行这个不同于其他项目
which just offered me Gradle and j unit
刚给我Gradle和j单位
I can run this with arquillian j unit if
如果可以，我可以使用Arquillian j unit运行它
I want to so I choose this option and it
我想要，所以我选择了这个选项
allows me to choose the container to run
让我选择要运行的容器
so here I'm going to configure a new
所以在这里我要配置一个新的
york alien container I'm going to use an
纽约外星人的容器，我要使用
embedded well de contain them so let's
嵌入式包含它们，所以让我们
okay that select this container and run
好的，选择此容器并运行
it now
现在
running test this way is that I can run
这样运行测试就是我可以运行
it in a bunch of different containers in
它放在一堆不同的容器中
a fairly lightweight way the IDE is
IDE相当轻巧
going to take care of downloading the
将照顾下载
right dependencies of setting at the
设置的正确依赖性
right environment I don't have a lot of
合适的环境我没有很多
configuration to manage for this I don't
配置为此管理我不
have to use a maven or Gradle to
必须使用Maven或Gradle来
download all the right dependencies the
下载所有正确的依赖项
idea is going to do this for me and you
想法将为我和你做到这一点
can see as per usual it's giving me what
可以像往常一样看到它给我什么
I'd expect to see and test results
我希望看到并测试结果
whether this test passed or failed if I
如果我该测试通过还是失败
want to I can I can configure those I
想要我可以配置那些我
can configure more of those
可以配置更多这些
configurations for our Killian as well
我们的Killian的配置
and so that's kind of the additional
所以这是额外的
support we've added for our Killian
我们为Killian添加的支持
let's have a look at dhaka Sedaka
让我们来看看dhaka Sedaka
obviously is a has been one of those
显然是其中之一
rising trends over the last few years
过去几年的上升趋势
and shows certainly no sign of
而且肯定没有迹象
diminishing so we as per usual we are
减少，所以我们像往常一样
adding as many feature new features as
添加尽可能多的功能新功能
we can to to support developers who are
我们可以支持那些
using these sorts of things so I have
使用这些东西，所以我有
dug up and running I'm going to connect
挖出并运行我要连接
to it as an application server so what I
作为应用程序服务器，所以我
did is I needed to enable the docker
我需要启用docker吗
plugin first so I've got dr. integration
首先插件，所以我有博士。积分
enabled this is a plug-in it's not
启用这是一个插件，不是
necessarily it doesn't necessarily come
不一定一定要来
built into intelligence to begin with
内置于智能中
I've also had to add and I've had to add
我还必须添加，并且我必须添加
a darker cloud deployments this is all
黑暗的云部署就这些
covered in an earlier webinar around the
在较早的网络研讨会中，
new docker features which came in and
出现了新的Docker功能
IntelliJ 14.1 so I don't want to cover
IntelliJ 14.1，所以我不想讲
that in too much detail but the point is
那太详细了，但是重点是
that I can see I can see dr. down here
我可以看到我可以看到博士。在这里
one of the new features is the ability
新功能之一是能力
to create a new container from an image
从图像创建新容器
so I'm going to create container here
所以我要在这里创建容器
here I have
我在这里
all the options for creating this
创建此的所有选项
container I can tweak this exactly how I
容器我可以精确地调整它
want to so for example i can define my
想要这样，例如我可以定义我的
port bindings i can define length i can
端口绑定，我可以定义长度，我可以
define my environment variables i can do
定义我可以做的环境变量
all of this through the UI if i want to
如果我想通过UI进行所有这些操作
if I'm used to doing things the command
如果我习惯于执行命令
line weight then I can pass in my
线重然后我可以通过
command line options here so I can copy
命令行选项，以便我可以复制
these from wherever I was doing my
这些无论我在哪里做
command line configuration in the past
过去的命令行配置
and IntelliJ IDEA will pass these into
IntelliJ IDEA会将它们传递给
something more suitable for the for the
更适合的东西
configuration here and obviously I can
在这里配置，显然我可以
also select a basin file here as well so
在这里也选择一个盆地文件
i can select my my daugher JSON file I
我可以选择我的女儿JSON文件
can use a combination of my command line
可以结合使用我的命令行
arguments and my you i defined arguments
参数和我，我定义了参数
and once I've done that it will deploy
一旦完成，它将部署
it and run it and I can attach this
运行它，我可以附加它
session and type into my console in we
会话并在我们的控制台中输入
are full support for dr. toolbox now and
全力支持博士。现在的工具箱和
the fact that's actually what I'm
我实际上就是我
running here on this machine so however
在这台机器上运行，所以
you configure ducker you should be able
您配置小鸭，你应该能够
to get up and running inside IntelliJ
在IntelliJ中启动并运行
IDEA without without too many problems
没有太多问题的IDEA
so far we've been kind of fairly Java
到目前为止，我们一直都相当Java
specific with this but as usual we've
与此特定，但像往常一样
also added support for other languages
还增加了对其他语言的支持
too so for groovy we've added support
对于常规，我们也增加了支持
for the Builder annotation so this
对于Builder注释，所以这
allows you to add the app builder
允许您添加应用构建器
annotation onto the top of one of your
注释到您的其中一个的顶部
groovy classes and have IntelliJ IDEA
常规类并具有IntelliJ IDEA
recognize this and provide you with
认识到这一点并为您提供
autocomplete for things like the Builder
自动完成诸如Builder之类的功能
methods the setters and the Gators and
方法的二传手和鳄鱼
so forth for in terms of scholar website
在学者网站方面如此
in terms of Scala we have a number of
就Scala而言，我们有很多
improvements including macro expansion
包括宏扩展在内的改进
extractor and like Java we can debug to
提取器，就像Java一样，我们可以调试到
stop at lambda expressions we have got
停下来，我们有lambda表达式
postfix completion for scholar if you
学者的后缀完成（如果您）
haven't had a look at postfix completion
没看过后缀完成
it's a really good way to allow you to
这是让您能够
keep continue
继续
typing so instead of having to move your
键入，而不用移动您的
cursor around the lines to perhaps
将光标放在线条周围，也许
extractive variable or so forth with
提取变量等等
postfix completion you can add things
后缀完成，您可以添加内容
onto the end of your line and have it
到您的行的末尾并拥有它
automatically create code view we've
自动创建我们的代码视图
also added support for in right in line
还增加了对in line的支持
refactoring to type aliases there is a
重构输入别名
number of detailed blog information
详细的博客信息数
about the scholar improvements in
关于学者的进步
IntelliJ IDEA 15 which are available on
IntelliJ IDEA 15可在
the blog and of course Kotlin being mean
博客，当然还有Kotlin是卑鄙的
to being the JetBrains JVM language baby
成为JetBrains JVM语言的宝贝
this is the m14 releases bundled in with
这是捆绑在一起的M14版本
IntelliJ IDEA 14 the plug-in is part of
IntelliJ IDEA 14插件是
sorry it's part of IntelliJ IDEA 15
抱歉，它是IntelliJ IDEA 15的一部分
there's it's no longer an additional
不再有额外的
plugin it's all built in part of the IDE
插件全部内置在IDE中
this I guess is kind of part of the
我想这是其中一部分
whole ramp up and process of getting us
整体提升和让我们的过程
ever closer to that 1.0 Kotlin release
更加接近1.0 Kotlin版本
so this should make it super easy to get
所以这应该使它超级容易获得
up and running with Kotlin if it's
和Kotlin一起运行
something you do want to try try playing
您想尝试玩的东西
with it so fully supported inside the ID
它在ID中得到了充分的支持
email and for the web frameworks we
电子邮件和网络框架，我们
haven't forgot about the web frameworks
并没有忘记网络框架
as always we're adding a lot of support
一如既往，我们增加了很多支持
for for the web technologies to so we've
为网络技术，所以我们已经
added support in typescript for
在打字稿中增加了对
typescript 1.6 features like
打字稿1.6功能如
intersection types type guard functions
交叉点类型类型保护功能
local types and and and also integration
本地类型和以及以及集成
with TF lint for polymer 1.0 we've added
我们为聚合物1.0添加了TF绒毛
basic support but the thing i want to
基本的支持，但我想
show you is our support for react so
表明你是我们对反应的支持，所以
open up a react project so like any
像任何人一样打开一个React项目
other supported language
其他支持的语言
what you get with IntelliJ IDEA if you
如果您使用IntelliJ IDEA会得到什么
are if you're using me act is that you
如果你在用我，那就是你
get auto complete with all your expected
自动完成您的所有预期
features so it makes it much much easier
功能，使它变得容易得多
to develop with this library once you've
一旦完成此库的开发
got it all set up so you can it will
完成所有设置，以便您可以
also suggest you a bunch of things which
也建议你一堆东西
are suitable for you I can also navigate
适合你我也可以导航
through these things so I can click
通过这些事情，我可以点击
command click through to find where
命令单击以查找位置
these things have been defined and I can
这些东西已经定义好了，我可以
also do things like I can look at which
也做类似我可以看的事情
wich parameter types are expected in
参数类型应该在
these method calls to so again it gives
这些方法再次调用它给
me some help and some guidance if I
如果我可以给我一些帮助和指导
wanted to I if I was written this myself
要我写我自己写的
it also gives me auto completion to
这也让我自动完成
allow me to select these custom types so
请允许我选择这些自定义类型
these these things comment comment box
这些这些东西评论评论框
and so forth have been defined inside
等等已经在里面定义了
this file and and IntelliJ IDEA is
这个文件和IntelliJ IDEA是
giving me support allowing me to like
给我支持，让我喜欢
these here if I want to I can also see
这些如果我想我也可以看到
for these custom types here I can also
对于这些自定义类型，我也可以
see the definition if I do need look
看定义，如果我确实需要看
control oh I then I can look at the
控制哦，然后我可以看看
definition here or I can click through
定义在这里，或者我可以点击
and it will take me to where this was
它将带我到这里
defined it also gives me autocomplete on
定义它也给我自动完成
my HTML for the react specific
我的特定于反应的HTML
attributes so I can do for example class
属性，所以我可以做例如类
name I'll automatically allow me to use
我会自动允许我使用的名称
those even for HTML inside the
那些甚至用于HTML
JavaScript and so if that's support for
JavaScript，如果可以的话
HTML inside the JavaScript then
然后在JavaScript中添加HTML
obviously we also have support for
显然，我们也支持
javascript inside our HTML here so I can
我们的HTML里面的javascript，所以我可以
type this and I can say more markup and
输入这个，我可以说更多标记，
it will give me my auto complete for
它会给我我的自动完成
that too so I get the full idea
那也是我的全部想法
experience regardless of whether I'm
无论我是否经验
trying to write HTML or JavaScript or
尝试编写HTML或JavaScript或
whatever for for reacts in this inside
在这里面做什么反应
intellij idea
聪明的主意
Dean and finally before we go on to any
院长，最后，在我们继续之前
further questions or drill down into
进一步的问题或深入研究
something in more in any more detail
更详细的内容
that people want to see we have updated
人们想看到我们更新了
database tools as well they've been a
数据库工具以及它们一直是
lot of improvements in the idea to
这个想法有很多改进
improve the way that you can work with
改善您的工作方式
your database inside your IDE I
您的IDE中的数据库
particularly find this really
特别是发现这个真的
interesting because it allows you to do
有趣，因为它允许您做
everything inside the ID without how to
ID内的所有内容都没有
leave and go to another tool so let's
离开并转到另一个工具，让我们
have a look at an example of this if we
看看这个例子，如果我们
go back to my java ee tutorial i can see
回到我的Java EE教程中，我可以看到
my databases window so this we've had
我的数据库窗口
the databases window for some time the
数据库窗口一段时间
window is not is not necessarily new and
窗口不一定是新的，
but what i can do is some of the things
但是我能做的是一些事情
that have changed is the data sources
发生变化的是数据源
and driver's window here has been
和司机的窗户在这里
modified to make it a bit easier to use
进行了修改，使其更易于使用
make it a bit prettier and i think most
使它更漂亮，我认为大多数
interestingly to me is the fact that you
对我来说有趣的是你
can modify your table right here so i
可以在这里修改您的表，所以我
can use an au I to create the changes
可以使用我来创建更改
that i want to see so i can remove this
我想看到的所以我可以删除这个
column if I want to I can add a new
栏，如果我想添加一个新的
column let's say a I don't know favorite
专栏，假设我不知道喜欢的
book I get autocomplete so I know that
这本书我会自动完成，所以我知道
I'm not not miss typing something so I
我不会错过任何键入的内容，所以我
get a new a new column here and you can
在这里获得新的新专栏，您可以
see the sequel script to you can also
看到续集脚本也可以
edit this if you want to and alter the
如果您想编辑此内容并更改
edits that you've made on your sequel
您对续集所做的编辑
scripts and it will apply those when
脚本，它将在
you're doing the refactoring you can
你正在做重构，你可以
also
也
indices so yes you can also add indices
索引，是的，您还可以添加索引
so if I want to I can add an index on
因此，如果我想添加索引
let's say I'm going to want to search on
假设我要搜寻
last name so i can add an index here on
姓氏，以便我可以在此处添加索引
last name and i can add foreign keys as
姓氏，我可以将外键添加为
well so i can add a new foreign key and
好吧，我可以添加一个新的外键，
with the target table which I at UConn
与我在UConn的目标表
doing this demo because i did not create
进行此演示，因为我没有创建
a second table oh but it foreign quito
第二张桌子哦，但它是外国基多
second table and you get all that extra
第二张桌子，你得到所有额外的东西
autocomplete to help you do that so if i
自动完成功能可以帮助您做到这一点，如果我
delete that and run this I should get it
删除并运行它，我应该得到它
should remove one oh look I've done too
应该删除一个哦，我也做过
much in one go let's cancel this and try
一口气让我们取消此尝试
it again it would be no fun if we didn't
再次，如果我们不这样做，那将毫无乐趣
see any errors so let's just let's be
看到任何错误，所以让我们成为
less ambitious and just try and remove
雄心勃勃，只需尝试删除
these two columns here okay then we get
这两列都可以，然后我们得到
those changes come through here now
这些变化现在通过这里
let's have a look
我们来看一下
table editor term now um IntelliJ IDEA
表格编辑器术语，现在为IntelliJ IDEA
15 has added a lot of support for being
15增加了很多支持
able to talk much more and much more
能够说话的越来越多
usefully to databases so that we can
对数据库很有用，以便我们可以
have more information about what the
有更多关于
database looks like what the table looks
数据库看起来像表一样
like all the things that you might you
喜欢你可能会遇到的一切
as a developer might want to do with
作为开发人员可能想做的
that database which allows it to work
该数据库可以正常工作
much more quickly in terms of doing
做起来快得多
things like bringing up the data in that
诸如在其中调出数据之类的东西
in that table or allowing you to alter
在该表中或允许您更改
stuff in the database so it's not really
在数据库中的东西，所以不是真的
something I can specifically demo other
我可以专门演示其他的东西
than it should work faster than it used
比它应该比以前更快地工作
to we have a specific support for my
我们对我有一个具体的支持
sequel postgres sequel and Microsoft
续集postgres续集和Microsoft
sequel mmm and oh yes and another new
续集，嗯，是的，另一个新
feature that you can do is when you
您可以做的功能是当您
bring up a table editor I can do a
调出表格编辑器我可以
search obviously sequel is kind of
搜索显然续集是一种
designed to do searching but if I've got
设计做搜索，但是如果我有
my first page of results or some set of
我的第一页结果或一组
results I can also search these results
结果我也可以搜索这些结果
for something which which aren't
对于不是的东西
particularly looking for so here I can
特别是在这里寻找
find myself and finally let's bring up a
找到自己，最后让我们提出一个
file actually uses the sequel so let's
文件实际上使用了续集，所以让我们
say we have this sequel here and I can
说我们在这里有这个续集，我可以
run this in a console and so I've run
在控制台中运行它，所以我运行了
this and I can see I can see the results
这个，我可以看到我可以看到结果
of it here
在这里
if I try and run it a second time it
如果我尝试第二次运行
gives me the option to rewrite this or
给我选择重写此选项或
perhaps open a new console this kind of
也许用这种方式打开一个新的控制台
super useful obviously if you want to
超级有用的如果你想
run a bunch of different queries or
运行一堆不同的查询或
variations on the query so that you can
查询的变体，以便您可以
see and perhaps what the differences are
看，也许有什么区别
so let's say let's order by ID desk and
假设我们通过ID Desk和
try rerunning that oops or not this is
尝试重新运行哦，这不是
what happens when you try and wing it
当您尝试使用它时会发生什么
you're going to get an error but anyway
你会得到一个错误，但无论如何
you get the idea if I was running in
你知道我是否在跑步
front if I was running a different query
如果我正在运行其他查询
or a variation on the same query I could
或同一查询的变体
see the results of those two queries
查看这两个查询的结果
side by side so I could see what they
并排，所以我可以看到他们
look like thank you everybody for
貌似谢谢大家
joining us and I believe that is the end
加入我们，我相信这就是结局
of our introduction to intellij idea of
我们介绍intellij的想法
15 thanks a lot
15非常感谢